Finding Aid for the Susan Sontag Papers LSC.0612
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1942-2004
  - Spiegelman, Art., 1993-1994. (Box 142, Folder 39)
  - Spies, Werner (German art historian)., 1990 March 30. (Box 142, Folder 40)
  - Spooner, Casey (musician in Fischerspooner)., 2003 September 6. (Box 142, Folder 41)
  - Stanica, George., 1995 September 3. (Box 142, Folder 42)
    2 items. Original letter and photocopy.
  - Starr, Kenneth I., 2001 October 25. (Box 142, Folder 43)
  - Stehlik, Milos., 2001 December 20. (Box 142, Folder 44)
  - Stein, Bonnie Sue (Performing Arts Journal and GOH Productions)., 1990, 1992-1993. (Box 142, Folder 45)
    4 items. Includes photographs
  - Stein, Douglas (set designer)., 1990 March 19. (Box 142, Folder 46)
  - Stein, Elliot (American film critic)., 1966-1968, no dates. (Box 142, Folder 47)
    19 items.
  - Stein, Jean., 1994, 1996, 1998. (Box 142, Folder 48)
  - Steinbach, Meredith., 1985 July 17. (Box 142, Folder 49)
  - Steiner, George (writer and English professor)., 1982 May 24. (Box 142, Folder 50)
  - Stephane, Nicole (French actor, film producer)., 1992-2001, no dates. (Box 142, Folder 51)
  - Stermer, Dugald (artist, graphic designer)., no date. (Box 142, Folder 52)
  - Stern, Fritz and Elizabeth Sifton (writers)., 1997, 2003. (Box 142, Folder 53)
  - Stewart, Susan (Temple University)., 1990-1991. (Box 142, Folder 54)
  - Stewart, Walker M., 1972 November 15. (Box 142, Folder 55)
  - Stimpson, Catherine (New York University Dean)., 1975, 1996-2003, no dates. (Box 142, Folder 56)
  - Strachan, Pat (Farrar Straus & Giroux Executive Editor)., 1986 June 27. (Box 142, Folder 57)
  - Straus, Dorothea (wife of Roger Straus)., 1964, 1977, 1993-2001, no dates. (Box 142, Folder 58)
  - Straus, Nina Pelikan (wife of Roger Straus III)., 1992 August 28. (Box 142, Folder 59)
  - Straus, Rachel (dance critic, granddaughter of Roger Straus)., 2002 April 24. (Box 142, Folder 60)
  - Streep, Meryl (actress)., no date. (Box 142, Folder 61)
  - Sunder-Plassman, Andrea (artist)., 1990, 1991. (Box 142, Folder 62)
  - Surratt (Paul Goodman tribute)., 1992 August 27. (Box 142, Folder 63)
  - Susnik, Marjetica., 1996, 1997. (Box 142, Folder 64)
  - Sutherland, Donald (American critic)., 1964 July 13. (Box 142, Folder 65)
  - Sweeney, Francis X. (Boston College)., 1975 July 22. (Box 142, Folder 66)
  - Swenson, Gene? (art critic, writer)., 1966 February 14. (Box 142, Folder 67)
  - Syberberg, Hans Jurgen (German filmmaker)., 1978-1997, no dates. (Box 143, Folder 1)
    29 items.
  - T - General file., 1967 January 20. (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Tacou, Laurence (Director of Editions de L'Herne)., [no year] October 1. (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Takahashi, Yasunari (Japanese writer, translator)., 1980-1999, no date. (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Tamas, Gaspar M. (Hungarian philospher and political leader)., 1985-2003. (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Tancock, John L., 1987 July 10. (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Tanning, Dorothea (American artist)., 1986. (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Tarr, Bela (Hungarian film director)., 1994-1996. (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Taubes, Ethan, Tania, and Susan (philosopher, writer)., 1978-2004. (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, Harold., [no year] December 11. (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, Paul (dancer/choreographer)., 1985-1994. (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Taylor, Rachel., 1995 July 19. (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Teschke, Holger (theatre director)., 1999, no date. (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Thacher, Anita and Ken., no date. (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Tharoor, Shashi., 1997. (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Thek, Paul (American artist)., 1965-1987, 1992-1997. (Box 143, Folder 16)
    55 items. Letters are fragile and contain original drawings and watercolors
  - Thompson, Lianne., 1992 September 12. (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Thompson, Mark., 2002 January 20. (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Thurman, Judith., 2002, 2003. (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Tilbrook, Geraldina-Maria., 2003. (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Tipton, Jennifer (lighting designer)., 1996, 2001. (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Tomin, Julius., 1981 October 8. (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Trahan, Elizabeth., 1986 June 1. (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Treglown, Jeremy (editor of the Times Literary Supplement)., 1987, 2002, 2003. (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - Trilling, Diana and Lionel (critic)., 1967-1986. (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Tristman, Richard., no date. (Box 143, Folder 26)
  - Trobitius, Jorg., 1997. (Box 143, Folder 27)
  - Trow, George W., 1992 May 19. (Box 143, Folder 28)
  - Tuten, Frederic (American writer)., 1990-2004. (Box 143, Folder 29)
  - Uchida, Mitsuko (Japanese pianist)., 1989-2003. (Box 143, Folder 30)
  - Untermeyer, Louis (critic)., 1966. (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Updike, John (American writer)., 1980-1989, 2001. (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Ustinov, Andrei (Russian translator)., 1997-2003. (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Valenzuela, Luisa (Argentinian writer)., 1983-2003. (Box 144, Folder 4)
    23 items. Includes photographs of art project from Giancarlo Puppo
  - Valladares, Armando (Cuban dissident)., no date. (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - van den Eynde, Bart and Ivo van Hove (Dutch dramaturg and theatre director)., 2001. (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Van Sant, Gus (American film director)., 1995 April 25. (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Vanthan, Meas., 1968, 1972. (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Varda, Agnes., 1991 September 23. (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Veloso, Caetano (Brazilian musician)., 2002. (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Vercelloni, Isa Tutino (Italian writer)., 1995 August 29. (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Viereck, Peter (poet, critic)., 1988-2000, no date. (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Villani, Tony (filmmaker)., 1992-1993. (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Vinoly, Rafael (South American architect)., 2003. (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - von Boehm, Gero (German writer, filmmaker)., 1993-2002. (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - von Pilar, Ulrike (Doctors Without Borders)., 2001-2003. (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - von Tippelskirch, Karina Kranhold (German translator)., 2000-2003, no date. (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - von Trotta, Margarethe., 1999 March 28. (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - Voznesensky, Andrei (Russian poet)., 1989-1990. (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Vulliamy, Ed (English writer, journalist)., 2002-2003, no dates. (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - W - General file., no date. (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Wada, Junko (Japanese performance artist)., 2003 September 15. (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Wajda, Andrzej (Polish filmmaker)., 1994. (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Wakoski, Diane., 1990 July 18. (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - Walcott, Derek., 1990 January 23. (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Walsh, Bernard., 1994 September 24. (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Walsh, Robert (Vanity Fair legal affairs editor)., 1988-2003. (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - Wanger, Shelley., 1983, no date. (Box 144, Folder 28)
    2 items. 1983 item from Box 265, Folder 2
  - Warburg, Fredric J. (English publisher)., 1969 January 27. (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - Warner, Marina (English writer)., 1991, no date. (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Warshow, Paul (critic)., 1976 September 28. (Box 144, Folder 31)
  - Wasserman, Steve (Los Angeles Times Review of Books editor)., 1990-2003. (Box 144, Folder 32)
  - Wastberg, Per (Swedish journalist, former president of International PEN) and Olle (Consul General)., 1983-2002, no date. (Box 144, Folder 33)
  - Waters, Alice (American chef, owner of Chez Panisse)., 1998-2001. (Box 144, Folder 34)
  - Waters, Lindsay (Director of the University of Minnesota Press)., 1991 March 18. (Box 144, Folder 35)
  - Watson, Jeannette (Books & Co.) ?., 1996. (Box 144, Folder 36)
  - Weaver, Fritz., 1963 September 20. (Box 144, Folder 37)
  - Webb, Jack (San Diego Union-Tribune)., 1998, no dates. (Box 144, Folder 38)
  - Wechsler, Judith (American art historian)., 1965-2000. (Box 144, Folder 39)
  - Weems, Marianne (Director, Builders Association)., 1996-2002, no dates. (Box 144, Folder 40)
  - Wenkart, Henny (American writer, publisher)., 1980 September 23. (Box 144, Folder 41)
    1 item. Includes 1962 letter from Sontag
  - Werly, Jacqueline., 1987 July 21. (Box 144, Folder 42)
  - Weschler, Lawrence (American writer)., 1995, 2002. (Box 144, Folder 43)
  - West, Alison (writer)., 1999 July 7. (Box 144, Folder 44)
  - West, Paul., 1985 April 2. (Box 144, Folder 45)
  - West, Susan., [1996]. (Box 144, Folder 46)
  - Westling, Renee and Len., 1988, 1990. (Box 144, Folder 47)
  - White, Edmund (American writer)., 1982, 2002. (Box 144, Folder 48)
  - White House., 1997-1999. (Box 144, Folder 49)
  - Wichmann, Dominik., 2003 August 27. (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Wieseltier, Leon (New York Review of Books, New Republic)., 1976-2000. (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Wilk, Larry., 1967 August 27. (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Willen, Drenka (Helen and Kurt Wolff Books editor)., 1985 January 4. (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Charlie., 2001. (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Wilson, Millie (artist)., 1990-2002. (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, Robert (theater producer, playwright)., 1982-2004. (Box 145, Folder 7)
    64 items.
  - Winterberg, Hans (German Book Review editor)., 1993. (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Wintour, Anna (Vogue editor)., no date. (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Witkin, Joel Peter (American artist, photographer)., 1990 April 15. (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Wohlstetter, Albert., 1996. (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Wolf, Christa (German writer)., 1989 July 14. (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Wolff, Helen., 1981. (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Wong, Shawn., 1996 May 13. (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Wood, James (American writer, literary critic)., 1991-2000, no date. (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Wood, Michael (American writer)., 1994-1995, 2002. (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Wooster Group., 2000, 2003. (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - Worth, Irene., 1992 December 27. (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Wrong, Dennis (American sociologist)., 1982 February 24. (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Xirau, Ramon (Mexican critic)., 1962, 1964. (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Yang, Lian (Chinese poet)., 1997-2001. (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Yates, Peter., 1979 June 27. (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Young, John Bell (pianist)., 1990 November 7. (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Young, Marguerite (American writer)., 1996. (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Youngerman, Jack (American artist)., 1971 September 6. (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Zagajewski, Adam (Polish writer)., 1989-2003. (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - Zank, Ric (books and manuscripts dealer)., 1994. (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - Zannoni, Giovannella (Italian film producer)., 1970-1975. (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - Zeppetelli, John., 1993 May 17. (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - Zerner, Henri., 2003 April 9. (Box 145, Folder 30)
  - Zolt, Marvin (accountant)., 1990-1991. (Box 145, Folder 31)
  - Zuckerman, Julie., ca. 2001. (Box 145, Folder 32)
  - Zurcher, Ariane., 1991-1992, 1999. (Box 145, Folder 33)
  - Unknown - General file., 1962-2003. (Box 145, Folder 34)
    66 items. Includes photographs and inserts from library series. Postcards from Box 236 Folder 1, Box 245 Folder 1, Box 250 Folder 2
  - Accessions 2012
    - Bentivoglio, Leonetta (Theater and dance journalist)., 1984 October 26. (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Berlin [?], Isaiah (British philosopher)., 1957 November 15. (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Breslin, Charles P., 1993 December. (Box 333, Folder 3)
      3 items. Poem to Susan Sontag.
    - Brodsky, Joseph (Russian poet and essayist)., 1978, no date. (Box 333, Folder 4)
      5 items. See also Box 137, folder 7.
    - Chester [?], Alfred (Writer)., 1961 June 1, no date. (Box 333, Folder 5)
      3 items. Includes letter addressed to Maria Irene Fornes.
    - Childs, Lucinda (American postmodern dancer and choreographer)., 1982-1983, no date. (Box 333, Folder 6)
      12 items. See also Box 83, folder 24.
    - Clarke, Esther., 1949 September 1. (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Donoughue, Bernard., no date. (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Farber, Joyce., no date. (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Fries, Kenny (Poet)., 1996 Aug 12. (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Grumbauch, Doris., 2000 March. (Box 333, Folder 11)
      3 items. Includes card signed by Helena Modjeska (Polish actress), 1879.
    - Hodgkin, Howard (English painter) and Peattie, Anthony (English opera critic)., 2002 September 9-21. (Box 333, Folder 12)
      4 items. See also Box 88, folder 1.
    - Kobata, Kazue (Japanese author and curator)., 2004 August 5. (Box 333, Folder 13)
      4 items. Includes pouch with talisman.
    - Kollisch, Eva (Feminist)., 1968 April 3. (Box 333, Folder 14)
      2 items. See also Box 81, folder 34 [Berliner, Eva].
    - Leibovitz, Annie (Photographer)., 1989, no date. (Box 333, Folder 15)
      15 items. Includes postcard to Leibovitz from Noriko Miyamoto.
    - Neier, Aryeh (Human rights activist)., 1984 September 28, no date. (Box 333, Folder 16)
      2 items. See also Box 139, folder 6.
    - Polukhina, Valentina (Russian scholar) and Weissbort, Daniel (Poet and translator)., 2004. (Box 333, Folder 17)
      3 items. Includes printed photograph of Susan Sontag, Valentina Polukhina and Daniel Weissbort; see also Box 140, folder 5.
    - Rieff, David (Son)., 1970 January 20-February 10, no date. (Box 333, Folder 18)
      7 items. See also Box 140, folder 34.
    - Ryle, Gilbert (British philosopher)., 1957 October 18. (Box 333, Folder 19)
    - Sohmers Zwerling, Harriet., 1957, no date. (Box 333, Folder 20)
      7 items. See also Box 142, folder 32.
    - Sontag, Judith (Sister)., 1950-1959. (Box 333, Folder 21)
      6 items. See also Box 83, folder 33.
    - Sontag, Mildred (Mother)., 1942-1960, no date. (Box 333, Folder 22)
      61 items. Includes letter to Mildred Sontag from Charles H. Niles regarding inquiry into Susan's eligibility for youngest college instructor in the United States.
    - Sontag, Nat (Stepfather)., 1987, no date. (Box 333, Folder 23)
    - Stephane, Nicole., 2000 September 9, no date. (Box 333, Folder 24)
      4 items. Includes photograph and flyer for film retrospective; envelope addressed to Annie Leibovitz and Susan Sontag; see also Box 142, folder 51.
    - Taubes, Jacob (German sociologist and theologian)., 1958. (Box 333, Folder 25)
    - Unknown - General file., 1958-2004, no date. (Box 333, Folder 26)
      35 items. Includes greeting cards, letters, love notes, postcards, telegrams and fragments, many with only first names and unidentified or missing surnames.
    - Wieseltier, Leon (New York Review of Books, New Republic)., 1999, December 26. (Box 333, Folder 27)
      1 item. See also Box 145, folder 2.
- Series 2: Juvenalia, ca. 1939
  Childhood drawings and writing.
  - Writing practice in pencil on newsprint., circa 1939. (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Drawings in crayon on newsprint., circa 1939. (Box 295, Folder 2)
- Series 3: School Material, 1949-1951
  Sontag's notes, papers, and other schoolwork from junior high school through graduate school.
  - Sub-series 3.1 Sontag's schoolwork from junior high school, circa 1943-1945; 2 folders
    - Notebooks, circa 1943 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      Spelling notebook; Geography class workbook. 2 items. Workbork pages signed Sue Rosenblatt
    - Saga of the Soviets by Sue Rosenblatt, circa 1945 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      Report about Russia and its role in World War II. 62 pages. Includes pencil drawings by Sontag and clippings taped in
  - Sub-series 3.2 Sontag's high school schoolwork and school newspaper., 1947-1949; 1 folder and 1 oversize folder
    - The Arcade., 1948 October 1 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      North Hollywood High School newspaper. 2 items. Sontag (in photo on front page): editor-in-chief and film critic.
    - Reports and papers for various classes, 1947-1949. (Box 146, Folder 12)
      12 items. Includes writing on The Magic Mountain and Sigmund Freud.
  - Sub-series 3.3 Sontag's notes and papers from UC Berkeley, UC Los Angeles, and University of Chicago, 1949-1951; 8 folders
    - History test in University of California blue book, 1949 March 15 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      1 item. Map inserted.
    - Humanities course assignments, 1949. (Box 146, Folder 14)
      18 pages.
    - "Observation, Interpretation, Integration" spiral notebook, 1949-1951. (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - "Observation, Interpretation, Integration" loose notes and handouts for the class., 1949-1951. (Box 147, Folder 1)
      99 pages. Papers were inserted in spiral notebook
    - "Literary Criticism", 1950. (Box 147, Folder 2)
      1 item. Back cover of notebook missing
    - "Literary Criticism" loose note pages., 1950. (Box 147, Folder 3)
      19 pages.
    - Analyses of Joseph Conrad's works, 1950. (Box 147, Folder 4)
      5 items (76 pages).
    - B.A. Thesis on "Nightwood" by Djuna Barnes, 1950. (Box 147, Folder 5)
      25 pages. Incomplete copy
  - Sub-series 3.4 Sontag's notes, syllabi, and papers from Harvard graduate school and Oxford, 1953-1957; 5.25 boxes (2.63 lin. ft.)
    - Philosophy of Science course notebook, 1953. (Box 147, Folder 6)
      1 item. Front and back cover detached. 1 loose paper inserted.
    - Notes on Kant, 1953. (Box 147, Folder 7)
      24 pages.
    - English course notes and paper (Machiavelli, Castiglione), 1953-1954. (Box 147, Folder 8)
      27 pages.
    - English course notes and papers (Sir Thomas More), 1953-1955 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      58 pages.
    - English course exams, 1954-1955. (Box 147, Folder 10)
      2 items and 4 pages.
    - English course notes, papers (Stuart and Tudor drama), 1954-1955. (Box 147, Folder 11)
      48 pages.
    - English course notes, papers, and exams (Stuart and Tudor drama), 1954-1955. (Box 148, Folder 1)
      2 items and 21 pages.
    - English course spiral notebook (Stuart drama)., 1954-1955. (Box 148, Folder 2)
      1 item. 8 loose note pages inserted
    - Philosophy course typescript notes (Metaphysics)., 1955. (Box 148, Folder 3)
      60 pages.
    - Philosophy course typescript notes (Metaphysics)., 1955. (Box 148, Folder 4)
      54 pages.
    - Metaphysics courses notes and papers (course numbers 156, 157, 259, 260), 1954-1956. (Box 148, Folder 5)
      1 blue book, 3 article excerpts, 2 folders, and 115 pages.
    - Philosophy course typescript notes, 1955. (Box 148, Folder 6)
      67 pages. Pages were in black vinyl spring binder. 1 loose paper inserted.
    - Philosophy course typescript notes, 1955 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      1 item and 65 pages. Pages were in black vinyl spring binder.
    - Church History course notes and papers, 1955. (Box 148, Folder 8)
      75 pages.
    - Church History course notes and papers, 1955. (Box 149, Folder 1)
      1 item and 49 pages.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook and paper (Ethical Theory), 1955-1956. (Box 149, Folder 2)
      1 item and 12 pages.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook and paper (Ethical Theory), 1955-1956. (Box 149, Folder 3)
      65 pages. Pages were inserted in spiral notebook.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook, 1955-1956. (Box 149, Folder 4)
      1 item. 9 loose pages inserted
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Plato), 1955-1956. (Box 149, Folder 5)
      1 item. 29 loose pages inserted.
    - Philosophy course notes and papers, 1955-1956. (Box 149, Folder 6)
      1 blue book, 1 folder, and 66 pages. Includes Sarah Lawrence College note dated 1959 with Plato notes on verso.
    - Humanities course notes, 1955-1957. (Box 149, Folder 7)
      104 pages. Pages were in light blue cloth covered 3-ring binder
    - Humanities, German, Psychology 203 course notes, 1955-1957. (Box 149, Folder 8)
      135 pages. Includes multiple semester course schedules. Pages were in light blue cloth covered 3-ring binder.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook and papers (Aristotle), 1956. (Box 150, Folder 1)
      1 item and 29 pages. Includes diary entry at back. 2 stapled pages inserted.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Locke, Berkeley, Hume), 1956. (Box 150, Folder 2)
      1 item. 19 loose pages and 2 stapled pages inserted. Back cover and last page detaching; all of notebook stained at upper left.
    - Metaphysics seminar notes and papers, 1956. (Box 150, Folder 3)
      1 printed article and 108 pages.
    - Ethics seminar spiral notebook, 1956?. (Box 150, Folder 4)
      1 item. 2 loose papers inserted
    - Philosophy course notes (German Classical philosophy, Professor Paul Tillich), 1956. (Box 150, Folder 5)
      65 pages.
    - Philosophy course notes (German Classical philosophy, Professor Paul Tillich), 1956. (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Philosophy course paper drafts and final version (Hegel), 1956-1957. (Box 150, Folder 7)
      83 pages.
    - Notes on Plato, Aristotle, Aquinas, Spinoza, and Leibniz., ca. 1955-1957. (Box 150, Folder 8)
      140 pages. Pages were in black binder.
    - Black cloth covered 3-ring binder., circa 1955-1957. (Box 151, Folder 1)
      1 item. In-law's name and address written on inside front cover.
    - Notes on Locke, Berkeley, Hume, circa 1955-1957. (Box 151, Folder 2)
      105 pages. Pages were in black binder
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Mind-Body Problem), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 3)
      1 item. 5 loose papers inserted
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Analysis of Law and Morals), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 4)
      1 item. 23 loose papers inserted.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Analysis of Law and Morals), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 5)
      1 item. Sontag's family tree on back pages.
    - Philosophy seminar spiral notebook (Causation), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Philosophy seminar notes (Causation), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 7)
      81 pages. Pages were inserted in spiral notebook.
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Spinoza), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Philosophy course spiral notebook (Spinoza), 1957. (Box 151, Folder 9)
      1 item. 8 loose papers inserted.
    - Philosophy seminar paper drafts, 1957. (Box 152, Folder 1)
      33 pages.
    - Philosophy of History notes, book excerpts, clippings, 1957. (Box 152, Folder 2)
      10 items and 16 pages.
    - Oxford course spiral notebook; England and France travel notes, 1957. (Box 152, Folder 3)
      1 item. 4 loose papers inserted.
    - Oxford course spiral notebook; shopping list, 1957. (Box 152, Folder 4)
      1 item. 1 clipping inserted. Back cover missing.
    - Oxford course spiral notebook, 1957. (Box 152, Folder 5)
      Includes: classmate list; to do list; travel notes; lines in others' handwriting.
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957. (Box 152, Folder 6)
      Includes typescript Moritz Schlick excerpt and Harvard student life guide guide.
    - Miscellaneous Philosophy course papers, circa 1953-1957. (Box 152, Folder 7)
      112 pages.
    - Miscellaneous English course papers, 1954-1955. (Box 152, Folder 8)
      97 pages.
  - Sub-series 3.5, 1947-1957; 1.50 boxes
    Material from the 2012 Accession. Junior High through Graduate school.
    - North Hollywood Junior High and High school materials, 1947-1949. (Box 342, Folder 1)
      18 items; includes class schedule, commencement program, drawings, assignments, school newspaper, and a high school reunion newsletter dated 1985.
    - University of Chicago student ID card, 1950-1951. (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - University of Connecticut materials, 1953-1954. (Box 342, Folder 3)
      2 items; typed description of Sontag's academic career, and housing remittance payment stub.
    - Radcliffe College transcript and student ID, 1955-1956. (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Application and statement for study abroad in England, 1956. (Box 342, Folder 5)
      14 pages; includes application for government grant, and typed statement drafts with holograph corrections and notes.
    - Oxford faculty listing, Humanities department, 1957. (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Prior, & the Naturalistic Fallacy., undated (Box 342, Folder 15)
      Assignment for Philosophy 256. Ca. 50 pages; includes typescript with holograph corrections, typed and holograph notes and fragments.
    - Textbook "Humanities 2, Syllabus and Selected Readings", 1947 September. (Box 343, Folder 1)